{
    "subject": "resource/Howard_Reynold_Penn",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/British_Virgin_Islands",
    "human_readable": "Howard Penn was born in the British Virgin Islands.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9570925235748291,
            "question": "Is Howard Penn from the British Virgin Islands?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8985629677772522,
            "question": "Are there any famous people born in the British Virgin Islands besides Howard Penn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8774552345275879,
            "question": "Where was Howard Penn born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7604869604110718,
            "question": "When was Howard Penn born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.607927143573761,
            "question": "What nationality is Howard Penn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5548083782196045,
            "question": "Are there any interesting facts about Howard Penn's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.504934549331665,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Howard Penn's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4179205298423767,
            "question": "What is Howard Penn known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3154408931732178,
            "question": "What country are the British Virgin Islands part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25561460852622986,
            "question": "What is life like in the British Virgin Islands?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Howard Penn was born in the British Virgin Islands.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5606_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country are the British Virgin Islands part of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5606_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Howard Penn known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5606_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Howard Penn's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5606_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5606_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5606_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5606_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5606_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5606_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5606_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5606_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5606_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5606_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5606_55.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThis is because none of the documents provided contain information about Howard Penn's birthplace, let alone mentioning the British Virgin Islands. The documents mention different individuals with the name \"Howard\" or \"Howard Penn\", but they are from various locations such as Maryland, Los Angeles, Pennsylvania, and Washington D.C., which do not match the British Virgin Islands."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not mention Howard Penn being born in the British Virgin Islands. The information provided is about his life, family details, and career as a chef or actor but does not specify the place of his birth."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not mention Howard Penn being born in the British Virgin Islands.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple biographical entries state Howard Penn was born in the United States (Midwest, Los Angeles, Maryland).  There are also details about his family history and life events rooted in the US.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because there is no information provided about Howard Penn being born in the British Virgin Islands.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that Howard Penn was born in Maryland, United States. There is no mention of his birthplace being the British Virgin Islands.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}